<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>https://bitsllc.biz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bitsllc.biz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>iOS 14: Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-14-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-14-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Developing for iOS is a valuable and in-demand skill, but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t developed in the Apple world before, it can be surprisingly different.
In this course, iOS 14: Getting Started, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly get up and running using Xcode 12, Swift 5, and SwiftUI to build great iOS apps and tap into the latest features in iOS 14.
iOS 14 Getting Started
Course OutlineFirst, you&amp;rsquo;ll see the tools and learn how to create iOS apps with adaptive user interfaces that work on multiple devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing In-App Purchases on iOS</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/implementing-in-app-purchases-on-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/implementing-in-app-purchases-on-ios/</guid>
      <description>Monetizing apps is challenging. In this course, Implementing In-App Purchases on iOS, you’ll learn to offer digital products and services directly within your app as in-app purchases.
Implementing In-App Purchases on iOS
Course OutlineFirst, you’ll explore how to translate business requirements into digital products and configure them in App Store Connect and Xcode.
Next, you’ll discover how to build and test a store within your app using StoreKit.
Finally, you’ll learn how to make sure purchases made within your app are authentic, and unlock content that’s been purchased by your users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Debugging Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-debugging-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-debugging-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Bugs are bound to happen. Getting rid of them is an essential skill if you want to keep your sanity when building apps.
In this course, you will learn a set of thinking skills to couple with the fundamental tools that Xcode provides you for finding and fixing flaws in your apps.
🐞1.5 hours 🦟To the point 🐛Engaging storyline 🐜Relevant demos
iOS Debugging Fundamentals
Course OutlineFirst, you will learn to approach debugging situations with a set of principles for strategic problem solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iOS Data Persistence: The Big Picture</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-data-persistence-the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/ios-data-persistence-the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. Do a search on the topic of &amp;ldquo;saving data in iOS” and you&amp;rsquo;ll get dozens of search results mentioning at least six different frameworks and platforms, and a month’s worth of reading.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be nice to distill the possibilities down into just what you need in order to start down a path for persisting data in your app?
&amp;ldquo;iOS Data Persistence: The Big Picture” will be worth the hour of your time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudKit Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/cloudkit-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/cloudkit-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>At the core of developing a seamless and collaborative data sharing experience for Apple’s platforms is a thorough knowledge of CloudKit.
In this course, you’ll learn to leverage Apple’s flagship framework to achieve your app’s remote data storage and data sharing requirements.
First, you’ll learn how to configure CloudKit in your Xcode project and how to save, query, update, and delete data that your users store in iCloud.
Next, you’ll explore how to synchronize data across a user’s devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Data Fundamentals with Swift</title>
      <link>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/core-data-fundamentals-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bitsllc.biz/courses/core-data-fundamentals-swift/</guid>
      <description>Core Data is an extremely powerful framework for managing and persisting data on your users&amp;rsquo; devices. And let&amp;rsquo;s face it: saving data to your users&amp;rsquo; devices is inevitable. The question is, which data management and persistence technology you use when the time comes for you to tackle this challenge?
&amp;ldquo;Core Data Fundamentals with Swift&amp;rdquo; will give you the essential skills you need to architect an app to use Core Data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
